<div id="FrontPageContent"><div id="DailyUK"><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2667460/Hes-Luis-Suarez-bites-opponent-key-World-Cup-clash-against-Italy.html" data-desc="England and Italy are blowing 'bite' storm out of proportion says Suarez's lawyer as pictures reveal disgraced striker's previous 'attack' on SAME player a year ago">Pictures have emerged of Luis Suarez apparently trying to bite Italian striker Giorgio Chiellini 12 months before the ugly clash between the two in Brazil yesterday.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2665935/Cameron-facing-double-defeat-Europe-Brussels-ignores-renegotiation-plan-prepares-appoint-Juncker-president.html" data-desc="'He f****d it up, he doesn't get it': Poland's Foreign Minister turns on his friend Cameron over EU demands in leaked tape">Radek Sikorski, who was in the infamous Bullingdon Club with Boris Johnson at university in Oxford, accused Mr Cameron of 'incompetence' and 'stupidly' pandering to his eurosceptic backbenchers.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669244/Unwelcome-home-boys-Englands-flops-arrive-Manchester-disastrous-World-Cup-performance-sees-return-group-stages-finished.html" data-desc="Forget the Golden Generation, it's the X-BOX Generation: England's World Cup flops return early from Brazil empty-handed - apart from a free games consoles each
            Was this the moment Luis Suarez tried to bite the SAME Italian player a YEAR ago? Pictures reveal disgraced striker's previous 'attack' on World Cup victim as he faces two-year FIFA ban
           ">Members of the squad, including Arsenal's Jack Wilshere and Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain, were seen clutching the &#194;&#163;370 state-of-the-art consoles as they touched down at Luton Airport this afternoon. The consoles - and hopefully a copy of soccer video game FIFA 14 so they can brush up on their skills - were handed out as part of a sponsorship deal with the XBox manufacturer Microsoft.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669404/Single-mother-went-shopping-spree-council-mistakenly-50-000-bank-account-pay-prison.html" data-desc="Single mother who went on shopping spree after council mistakenly put £50,000 into her bank account will have to pay it back or go to prison">Michaela Hutchings, 23, spent &#194;&#163;9,000 on designer shoes, handbags and sunglasses in a two-day spending splurge after finding the transfer from Lichfield District Council, Staffordshire.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668976/3-3million-jobs-risk-Britain-leaves-EU-warns-Lib-Dem-Danny-Alexander-tensions-grow-Tories-Europe.html" data-desc="3.3million jobs at risk if Britain leaves the EU, warns Lib Dem Danny Alexander as tensions grow with Tories over Europe">In a speech in Washington today, Mr Alexander will release details of official Treasury analysis showing how many jobs depend on Britain remaining in the European Union.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668507/18-000-ton-waste-mountain-thats-caused-stink-cul-sac-three-years-Environment-Agency-legal-battle-site-owners-rubbish-removed.html" data-desc="Misery of the cul-de-sac that's been stuck next to a stinking 18,000-ton waste mountain for THREE YEARS">A 40ft mountain of waste has towered over a well-kept street in St Paul's Cray, in Bromley, south-east London (pictured main). Resident Alan Cowburn described the smell as 'overpowering'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669335/Drunk-thug-spared-jail-repeatedly-battering-girlfriend-face-free-AGAIN-magistrates-attacking-new-partner.html" data-desc="Thug who was spared jail for battering his girlfriend is free to go AGAIN by the same magistrates after attacking his NEW partner">Toby Hayden, 28, from Chippenham, Wiltshire, (left) sparked outrage when escaped with just community order after leaving his ex-lover Loretta Butterworth, 22, (right and inset) covered in blood following a vicious beating. Just 12 months on from the first attack, the labourer has been hauled in front of Chippenham Magistrates' Court again after assaulting his current girlfriend Amy Weaver, 27. Both times he was serving a sentence for a previous offence, but on each occasion, the court decided not to send the serial criminal to jail.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668999/Payday-giant-Wonga-fined-2-6million-sent-letters-FAKE-law-firms-scare-customers.html" data-desc="Why isn't Wonga in the dock? Fury at payday lender over bogus legal letters used to bully debtors">Britain's biggest money lender, founded by Errol Damelin (pictured), was found to have sent letters from made-up law firms threatening legal action, City watchdog the Financial Conduct Authority said.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669210/Victory-villagers-chase-travellers-green-police-warn-charged-FALSE-IMPRISONMENT-stand-off.html" data-desc="Victory for villagers as they chase travellers off their green... but police warn them they could be charged with FALSE IMPRISONMENT during stand-off">About 11 caravans drove in to the village of Nepcote, near Findon, West Sussex, yesterday. 50 residents then surrounded the village green - blocking the only entrance to the space with their cars.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2666213/Blair-growing-pressure-stand-Middle-East-peace-envoy-diplomats-demand-removal.html" data-desc="Blair must go! Ex-diplomats lead calls for PM who went to war on a lie to be axed as Middle East peace envoy">Signatories to an open letter, led by Mr Blair's former ambassador to Iran Sir Richard Dalton, describe his achievements in the region as &#226;&#8364;&#732;negligible&#226;&#8364;&#8482;.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668905/Bob-Crows-six-figure-nest-egg-Union-chief-leaves-100-000-partner-three-children-ex-wife-receives-nothing.html" data-desc="Bob Crow's six-figure nest egg: Union chief leaves £100,000 to partner and their three children but his ex-wife receives nothing">The former RMT chief&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s partner Nicola Hoarau, 50, who he fathered three children with, will receive &#194;&#163;106,000. But his ex-wife Geraldine Horan misses out.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669427/From-Syria-Iraq-Kenya-Malaysia-How-new-era-Islamic-fundamentalism-spreading-fear-chaos-world.html" data-desc="From Syria to Iraq, Kenya to Malaysia: How new era of Islamic fundamentalism is spreading fear and chaos around the world">Over the last month, the world's media has been awash with gruesome images of barbarism - pulled into sharp focus in recent days with the barrage of horrific videos and hate-filled messages pouring onto the internet from ISIS in Iraq. They include armed militant children as young as eight watching as an Iraqi prisoner is executed, terror attacks in Kenya and brutal kidnappings in Nigeria. Another form of religious extremism has also gained widespread attention and outrage in Sudan, where a mother was handed the sentence for marrying a Christian man and was forced to give birth in shackles on death.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-2669301/David-Beckham-Tom-Cruise-stun-locals-enjoy-drink-pub-Londons-Notting-Hill.html" data-desc="Fancy a pint of Becks, Tom? Locals stunned as Cruise and Beckham enjoy a drink in a pub in London's Notting Hill">David Beckham and Tom Cruise left fans stunned as they enjoyed drinks at a pub in Notting Hill, London. The A-list pals opted against expensive restaurants and private members' clubs as they met up for a drink on Monday at Irish pub The Cow, and their boozy visit sent regulars into a frenzy. Patron Lisa Freid, who 'couldn't believe' her eyes, snapped a sneaky picture which she posted on her Instagram account.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668984/Theyre-Glastonburys-welly-wearing-army-march-Somerset-field-festival-gates-open-heavy-downpours-way.html" data-desc="Hunter wellies, posh grub and short shorts... here come the Glastonbury girls! Army of music fans descends as festival opens">Carrying tents and pushing wheel barrows, thousands of music fans began piling through the ticket gates into the 1,200-acre Somerset site ahead of the festivities. Queues have started to lengthen and traffic has started to build up as a steady stream of revellers began turning up. Many arrived with their raincoats and umbrellas packed, but forecasters have suggested they could become essential attire by the weekend with heavy rain forecast, while organisers have warned that the site could become 'quite muddy'. This year's festival sees Metallica, Kasabian and Arcade Fire headline the Pyramid Stage, alongside the likes of Lily Allen, Dolly Parton and the Pixies. Right: Saskia Hoccom, Hollie Clark and Maya Minter arrive well-prepared at the site. Inset: Kat Jackson, left, and Marie Barker from Derbyshire.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669363/Police-launch-huge-manhunt-90-year-old-woman-dragged-street-raped-walked-local-shop.html" data-desc="Police launch huge manhunt after 90-year-old woman is dragged off the street and raped as she walked to local shop">The attack took place in Rochdale, Greater Manchester (pictured) as the pensioner walked to a local shop, police said today.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/article-2669375/The-powerful-passports-world-revealed.html" data-desc="The world's most powerful passports: Infographic reveals which nations have the best access to the world (clue - Britain trumps the US, Canada AND Australia)">There aren't many nations who can travel the world at will, but British, Swedish and Finnish passports-holders certainly can.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/article-2668934/Severe-turbulence-Ryanair-flight-Spain-leaves-five-injured.html" data-desc="Passengers recount terror as severe turbulence on Ryanair flight to Spain leaves five injured and needing treatment">Two passengers and three cabin crew were hurt after the Boeing 737 hit an unexpected patch of turbulence on the approach to Reus airport.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-2667032/What-kind-emotional-eater-YOU-Take-quiz-learn-stop-heart-mind-ruining-diet.html" data-desc="What kind of emotional eater are YOU? Take the quiz and learn how to stop your heart and mind ruining your diet">If you're used to munching your way through a pack of biscuits because you're stressed, angry, or upset and you just want something to soothe you, you're in good company.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669194/Uruguay-TV-station-comes-defence-Suarez-bizarre-attack-British-media-saying-remember-Geoff-Hursts-second-goal-did-not-cross-line-1966.html" data-desc="'Don't forget Geoff Hurst's second goal didn't cross the line in 1966': Uruguay TV station comes to defence of Suarez with bizarre attack on British media">Uruguayan broadcaster Tenfield has blamed English journalists for drawing attention to Suarez's apparent attempt to bite Italian defender Giorgio Chiellini.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669217/Primark-dress-labels-allege-sweatshop-conditions-exhausting-hours.html" data-desc="'Forced to work exhausting hours': Shoppers' shock as they find hand-sewn labels protesting 'sweatshop conditions' in Primark clothing">High Street fashion chain Primark is investigating how labels were found sewn into clothing claiming 'sweatshop conditions' and 'exhausting hours'</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669436/Furby-toy-mother-bought-Argos-starts-swearing-gives-children.html" data-desc="Mother's anger after Furby she bought from Argos said 'f*** you' when she gave it to her children">Mother Louise Wilkinson was furious when a talking toy Furby she bought her daughter taught her to say: 'f*** you'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669406/Seriously-ill-schoolgirl-begged-doctors-not-send-home-died-multiple-organ-failure.html" data-desc="‘I’m dying’: Seriously ill schoolgirl begged doctors not to send her home after they told her to get ‘plenty of rest’ three days before she died from multiple organ failure">Amy Carter, 15, from Worcestershire, fell ill in 2009 with a sore throat and flu-like symptoms but was told by her GP to take paracetemol and 'get plenty of rest'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669885/From-micro-flat-three-bed-detached-What-Britains-average-home-price-And-London-shoeboxes-cost-4-000-month-rent.html" data-desc="From a micro flat to a three-bed detached... What you can buy across the country for Britain's average house price of £190,000">With the property market booming again, those desperately hoping to get on the ladder might be wise to look at where you get most for your money. This month Nationwide said the average UK property costs &#194;&#163;186,512, up more than 10 per cent on this time last year. This sort of money might only get you a run-down studio flat in London - but head to rural Scotland or Wales, and it could buy you a comfortable family home with spectacular views. Here are some tempting homes recently on sale, priced from &#194;&#163;180,000 to &#194;&#163;190,000.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669538/Explosion-rocks-mall-Nigerian-capital.html" data-desc="At least 21 killed in Nigerian shopping mall explosion one hour before country kicked off against Argentina in the World Cup">The blast in an upmarket district of Abuja, Nigeria's capital, happened just an hour before the national football team's group stage clash in Porto Alegre, Brazil. Witnesses said body parts were scattered near the Emab Plaza as black smoke could be seen from a mile away and surrounding buildings shook. No one has yet claimed responsibility but the attack bore hallmarks of the radical Islamist group Boko Haram, which has a stronghold in the north east of Nigeria and was responsible for the kidnapping of more than 200 schoolgirls.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669050/Are-likely-die-live-New-interactive-map-reveals-stark-differences-mortality-rates-country.html" data-desc="Are you more likely to die because of where you live? New interactive map reveals stark differences in mortality rates across the country">People living in Blackpool, Manchester and Middlesbrough are twice as likely to die as other parts of the country, according to the Office for National Statistics.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669958/Two-kitchens-Kate-Bill-palace-renovation-rockets-add-room-cosy-suppers.html" data-desc="Two kitchens Kate! Royal couple install second 'private, family kitchen' in addition to existing 350 sq ft room">The existing 350 sq ft kitchen has been refurbished at a reported cost to taxpayers of &#194;&#163;170,000 - but William and Kate also wanted a &#226;&#8364;&#732;private, family kitchen&#226;&#8364;&#8482;.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669980/Ban-fruit-juice-dinner-time-Health-experts-warning-parents-danger-sweet-drinks.html" data-desc="Ban fruit juice at dinner time: Health experts' warning to parents over danger of sweet drinks">Children should be given only water or milk and should not expect sweet drinks all the time, according to senior government advisers. They point out that fruit juices are helping fuel sharp rises in obesity rates, type 2 diabetes and heart disease. A typical teenager consumes 40 per cent more sugar than they should. Adults take in 13 per cent too much.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669429/BBC-accidentally-tells-viewers-prepare-rape-Glastonbury-latest-subtitles-blunder.html" data-desc="BBC accidentally tells viewers to 'prepare for rape' at Glastonbury in latest subtitles blunder">Viewers were warned to 'prepare for rape' rather than to 'prepare for rain' after the BBC News at 10 as weather experts predicted stormy weather would hit the UK this week.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669011/Watch-The-moment-police-custody-officers-surfed-Facebook-looked-porn-man-checking-died-cell-metres-away.html" data-desc="The shocking moment police officers were caught surfing Facebook and looking at porn while arrested man died in a cell a few yards away">Lloyd Butler, 39, died of a cardiac arrest while being detained at Stechford police station in the West Midlands on August 4 2010, an inquest decided yesterday.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2668941/Has-Rorys-ex-caught-eye-tennis-player-dubbed-Deliciano-Caroline-Wozniacki-blushes-shes-quizzed-possible-new-love-weeks-dumped-golfer.html" data-desc="Has Rory's ex caught the eye of tennis player dubbed Deliciano? Caroline Wozniacki blushes as she's quizzed about possible new love weeks after being dumped by golf star">Danish player Wozniacki, 23, giggled and blushed when asked about fellow player Lopez yesterday, describing him as 'a great guy'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669196/Nurse-left-fighting-life-stampeded-herd-cows-Lincolnshire-accused-999-operator-making-hoax-call.html" data-desc="Nurse who was left fighting for her life after being stampeded by a herd of cows was accused by 999 operator of making hoax call">Sarah Leonard suffered serious injuries including broken arms, a broken collarbone, broken jaw and several broken ribs during the incident in a field near Lincoln last November.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2669408/Rise-female-relationship-terrorists-Study-finds-women-controlling-aggressive-partners-men.html" data-desc="Rise of female 'relationship terrorists': Study finds women are more controlling and aggressive towards their partners than men">Psychologists from the University of Cumbria found women were &#226;&#8364;&#732;significantly&#226;&#8364;&#8482; more likely to be verbally and physically aggressive to men than vice versa.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669199/Hes-Pope-Francis-pulls-car-bless-disabled-woman-lying-stretcher-road.html" data-desc="He’s at it again! Pope Francis pulls over his car to bless disabled woman lying on a stretcher by the road">The leader of the Catholic Church had been returning from an appearance in Cassano allo Jonio in Calabria, southern Italy, when he spotted signs asking him to stop. Disregarding any danger - he had hours earlier threatened to excommunicate members of the Mafia - he ordered his driver to pull over and he got out to greet and bless the group. The Vatican&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s news.va website reported that people had been waiting with banners reading, 'Please Pope stop here to see an angel who has been waiting for you'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-2669424/The-perfect-female-celeb-Blake-Livelys-legs-Rihannas-abs-Jessica-Albas-smile.html" data-desc="Is this REALLY the 'perfect' female celebrity? Blake Lively's legs, Rihanna's abs and Jessica Alba's smile spliced together to create... the Bride of Frankenstein!">As well as drastically different skin tones for every body part, the combination of Rhianna's tattooed midriff and Carrie Underwood's angelic blonde hair is a little jarring.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2670071/Merkel-cuts-Cameron-adrift-backs-Juncker-EU-chief-PM-set-force-vote-time-saying-new-presidents-opposition-reform-unacceptable.html" data-desc="Merkel cuts Cameron adrift and backs Juncker for EU chief: PM set to force a vote for first time after saying new president's opposition to reform is unacceptable">The German Chancellor threw her weight behind former Luxembourg prime minister Jean-Claude Juncker for EC president, despite Mr Cameron&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s opposition.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-2669155/E-cigarettes-banned-public-normalise-smoking-says-leading-doctor.html" data-desc="E-cigarettes should be banned in public because they 'normalise' smoking, says leading doctor">Surgeon Ram Moorthy is due to present a motion calling for 'vaping' to be banned in the same places as smoking is prohibited at the British Medical Association's annual meeting.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2669886/Girl-work-experience-makes-major-cystic-fibrosis-breakthrough-Medical-students-discovery-prolong-lives-sufferers-help-diagnose-condition.html" data-desc="Girl on work experience makes major cystic fibrosis breakthrough: Medical student's discovery could prolong lives of sufferers and help diagnose the condition">Newcastle University student Jo Armstead, 21, (pictured) discovered that half of adults who suffer from the rare genetic disorder are infected with a common fungus while working at Wythenshawe Hospital in Manchester. Experts said the finding could help prolong the lives of patients with the debilitating lung condition, as well as help diagnose it where it had not been detected at birth.
      ...read</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-2669542/Rise-genetically-mutated-SUPER-RATS-Giant-rodents-immune-poison-spreading-rapid-speeds.html" data-desc="Rise of the genetically-mutated SUPER RATS: Giant rodents that are immune to poison are spreading at 'rapid speeds'">Genetic testing by Huddersfield University has revealed that rodents in the UK have developed a mutation that allows them to survive conventional poisons.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-2669067/My-jealous-friends-ditched-I-size-8-Super-slimmer-shed-SEVEN-stone-says-lost-mates.html" data-desc="'My jealous friends ditched me when I became a size 8': Super slimmer who shed SEVEN stone says she also lost all her pals">Standing at just 5ft 2in Fiona Hodge, 28, from Uxbridge, slimmed from a size 20 and 15st 4lb (left) to a size eight (centre and right) after she was devastated by her wedding pictures. She started a radical diet with the Cambridge Weight Plan and, with the support of husband Andy, quickly saw the pounds melt away. But Fiona claims her jealous friends have ditched her after her diet success - because they wanted her to be their fat friend.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2664787/Tory-MEPs-accused-hypocrisy-attacking-EU-waste-spending-30-000-taxpayer-funded-trip-Croatia.html" data-desc="Tory MEPs accused of hypocrisy after attacking the EU on waste - then spending £30,000 on taxpayer-funded trip to Croatia">Fourteen Tory MEPs &#226;&#8364;&#8220; some accompanied by spouses &#226;&#8364;&#8220; spent an estimated &#194;&#163;30,000 on flights, rooms at a five-star hotel and sumptuous local cuisine.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-2669169/Cara-Delevingne-launches-extraordinary-attack-fashion-bible-Vogue-claimed-fell-asleep-interview.html" data-desc="'Why do people in the industry lie so much?' Cara Delevingne launches extraordinary attack on fashion world after claims she fell asleep during Vogue interview">Writing about her meeting with Cara, American Vogue's Plum Sykes claimed that the party-loving model was late for their meeting and then fell asleep.</a></div><div id="DailyBusiness"><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-1607881/When-UK-rates-rise.html" data-desc="When will interest rates rise? Bank boss Mark Carney accused of sending mixed messages over timing of hike from 0.5%">Bank boss Mark Carney received a combative reception from MPS when he played down expectations of a rate hike this year that he himself has recently encouraged. Carney's testimony to the Treasury Select Committee prompted a jibe from Labour MP Pat McFadden that the Bank was 'behaving a bit like an unreliable boyfriend - one day hot, one day cold'.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/article-2269520/Best-paid-jobs-2012-Official-figures-national-average-UK-salaries-400-occupations.html" data-desc="Compare your pay to the national average in your job: League table of official UK salaries across 400 trades and professions">Midwives in the UK get paid on average &#194;&#163;29,248: so where does your salary fit into the national league table, and how does it compare to the average in your profession? Our table lists hundreds of Britain's jobs from company executives and doctors to van drivers, waiters and textile machine operators.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-1723571/This-Moneys-favourite-best-buy-Isas.html" data-desc="Our savings picks: This is Money's five favourite best buy cash Isas for 2014">We pick our five favourite cash Isas for savers. This is essential Isa reading and is kept up-to-date throughout the year</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664568/Iraq-oil-crisis-set-4p-litre-price-petrol-City-fears-grow-escalating-Middle-East-conflict-hits-fuel-supplies.html" data-desc="Oil crisis set to put 4p a litre on the price of petrol: City fears grow as escalating Iraq conflict hits supplies">Petrol retailers are warning of higher prices at the pumps as the bloodshed in Iraq sends the cost of oil soaring. And if a barrel of crude hits $120 the world could face a fresh economic crisis. The dramatic success of the jihadist group Isis in the Middle East has already pushed the price of crude to more than $115 a barrel. Just five months ago it was $85.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-1687576/What-mortgage-rates.html" data-desc="The best ever mortgage deals are vanishing, so should you grab a fix now? What next for mortgage rates?">Borrowers have seen the best of the spectacularly cheap mortgages vanish, especially the cream of the five-year fixed rates. So should you act now?</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664578/Celebrity-tax-avoiders-lose-fight-delay-paying-bills-experts-predict-wave-high-profile-bankruptcies.html" data-desc="Celebrity tax avoiders lose fight to delay paying bills up front ... and now experts predict wave of high-profile bankruptcies">Celebrity tax scheme promoters have failed to stop the Revenue forcing their clients to pay their bills up front. Experts predict a wave of high-profile bankruptcies. MPs sitting on the Finance Bill committee last week approved a plan to force investors in tax avoidance schemes to pay disputed bills immediately.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/holidays/article-2668234/How-cheaper-holiday-cash-HAGGLING.html" data-desc="The average family spends around €2,000 on a two-week trip abroad, so you can get cheaper holiday cash – by HAGGLING">In a bid to match the best internet rates, we tried haggling face-to-face in store - and were very surprised by the results.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/bills/article-2663470/The-energy-efficiency-measures-FOR-FREE-hold-them.html" data-desc="Want double glazing and new doors but don't want to pay for it? The energy efficiency measures you can get FOR FREE - and how to get hold of them">Gas boilers, double glazing, insulation and replacement doors are all up for grabs as part of the latest changes to the government&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s Green Deal. As much as &#194;&#163;2.61million has been given to households through the new Green Deal Home Improvement Fund during its first week. Here's how you can benefit.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-1596759/Ten-tips-buy-let.html" data-desc="Ten tips for buy-to-let: the essential advice for property investors and pick of the top mortgage rates">For many buy-to-let looks an attractive income investment in a time of low rates and stock market volatility. Read our top ten buy-to-let tips</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/bills/article-1591904/50-ways-save-money.html" data-desc="50 ways to save money: Simple steps to cut what you spend that could clear your debts or seriously boost your savings">To clear the average national household debt of &#194;&#163;13,000 at 6% interest with a monthly repayment of &#194;&#163;100 will take around 17 years. There are, however, plenty of simple ways to make significant savings on your regular spending that could clear your debt - or boost your savings - in less than a year. This is Money's top 50 &#226;&#8364;&#8220; updated &#226;&#8364;&#8220; money-saving tips may appear light-hearted but are deadly serious.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664535/The-mortgage-prisoners-Cap-income-multiples-trap-hundreds-thousands-borrowers.html" data-desc="The 'mortgage prisoners': Cap on income multiples will trap hundreds of thousands of borrowers">Hundreds of thousands of homeowners could become 'mortgage prisoners' if regulators introduce caps on income multiples to quell a house price bubble.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2663005/Bank-England-not-hold-rate-rise-says-official.html" data-desc="Bank of England will not ‘hold back’ on rate rise as another senior official hints that there will be soon be a hike">Ian McCafferty became the latest member of the central bank&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s rate-setting monetary policy committee to suggest that the first hike since 2007 is fast approaching.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/cardsloans/article-2666069/Over-50s-marry-kids-not-pay-debts-till-70s.html" data-desc="The 'second lifers' saddled with debt: Over 50s with new families may not pay off their debts till they hit 80">More than a quarter of over-50s who have re-married and had more children in their 30s or 40s say they still have a mortgage, with an average debt of &#194;&#163;73,881.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2665833/Buy-let-investors-expect-20k-income-properties-retirement.html" data-desc="Landlords 'expect a £20k income' from their properties in retirement - and third of all retirees considering buy-to-let">Landlords expect that more than half of their retirement income will come from their rental properties, an estimated &#194;&#163;19,785, according to a survey of 500 buy-to-let investors by Platinum Property Partners (PPP). On average investors expect their retirement income to total &#194;&#163;35,600, with the rest made up of state and private pensions, as well as other investments.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2656429/Lloyds-Bank-advisers-phoning-customers-dont-call-flags.html" data-desc="Lloyds Bank tells staff to phone customers about savings accounts - even if they have opted out of marketing calls">The bank justifies the practice by claiming the calls add value for customers &#226;&#8364;&#8220; and &#226;&#8364;&#732;help them to manage their money better&#226;&#8364;&#8482; so qualify as service, rather than marketing calls. However, branch staff, who wished to stay anonymous, say they build sales points, known within the bank as &#226;&#8364;&#732;needs met,&#226;&#8364;&#8482; if customers move money from current into savings accounts.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2665266/Morrison-fires-against-Aldi-Lidl-price-cuts.html" data-desc="Morrisons announces widespread price cuts in a bid to win the supermarket price war against budget chains Aldi and Lidl">It said reductions on 135 items would take effect from today, with an average drop in price of 14 per cent. The largest reduction is on Rocky chocolate bars.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/cardsloans/article-2665998/Millions-Brits-overspend-friends-dont-think-theyre-stingy.html" data-desc="'I can't afford it, but I'll get the round in': Millions of Brits overspend on nights out for fear of appearing stingy to friends">Almost half of Britons have admitted they have fallen into the red because they've overspent in their social lives, running up debts of &#194;&#163;1,260 on average over a year. And a third of these people estimate they spend an extra &#194;&#163;341-a-year because of 'pressure' they feel not to appear tight in front of their friends, even if it means cutting back on food or bill payments to cover these costs.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2667228/Sterling-tumbles-Bank-England-accused-rates.html" data-desc="Sterling slips as Bank of England accused of blowing hot and cold on outlook for interest rates">The pound dropped back below $1.70 to 1.6957 after governor Mark Carney appeared to play down the prospect of an interest rate rise before the end of the year.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2667060/Bar-workers-likely-paid-Living-Wage.html" data-desc="Bar and restaurant workers, shop staff, cleaners and hairdressers: The 10 jobs most likely to pay less than the Living Wage">The Living Wage Commission's report said 85 per cent of all bar staff and 810,000 sales and retail assistants are among Britain's most poorly paid people.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/cardsloans/article-2668974/Wonga-sent-customers-letters-non-existent-law-firms-says-FCA.html" data-desc="Outrage after regulators reveal Wonga pretended to be lawyers to scare 45,000 customers into paying up">The UK&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s biggest lender is to pay &#194;&#163;2.6million in compensation to customers for making up the law firms to pressure debtors into paying up.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/pensions/article-2661560/Forget-withdrawing-pot-youre-better-keeping-pension-invested-retirement.html" data-desc="Forget about withdrawing your whole pot - why you might be better off keeping your pension invested throughout retirement">Fidelity's Alan Higham says people reaching retirement from next April should not make any rash decisions, as it could result in them paying more tax than they need. In fact, if someone is already in a good pension scheme, they should consider keeping their money there as it may prove to be better value than many other products, he said.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2665012/Curbs-riskier-mortgage-lending-expected-BoEs-FPC-week.html" data-desc="Curbs on riskier mortgage lending expected from Bank of England this week in attempt to cool Britain's booming housing market">The latest decision from the BoE&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s Financial Policy Committee (FPC), which held its quarterly meeting last week, will be unveiled on Thursday.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/holidays/article-2664492/Hate-queueing-baggage-airports-Then-send-post-How-avoid-chore-lugging-heavy-suitcases-cut-holiday-costs.html" data-desc="Hate queueing for baggage at airports? Then send it by post: How to avoid the chore of lugging heavy suitcases - and cut holiday costs">Holidaymakers worried about paying hefty baggage charges at the airport this summer should consider posting on their suitcases before they travel. No-frills airlines such as Ryanair now charge as much as &#194;&#163;75 to check in a 20kg bag for popular high season flights - or &#194;&#163;45 if you do it online. This charge is for a one way trip so a return bill could be &#194;&#163;150.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664496/GCHQs-favourite-firms-secret-hacking-alerts-National-security-fears-raised-BTs-links-Chinese-company.html" data-desc="GCHQ's favourite firms to get secret hacking alerts: National security fears raised over BT's links with Chinese company">The spy agency is to provide classified information to private companies thought to include BT and Vodafone to guard against cyber attacks, but the move has raised security fears.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2668109/Rise-pensioner-landlords-lured-returns-5-cent.html" data-desc="Rise of pensioner landlords lured by returns of 5%: Older workers snap up rental properties in search of retirement income">A boom in older landlords is being driven by buyers seeking more income in retirement because their pension won&#226;&#8364;&#8482;t be as much as hoped.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2665872/Mortgage-supply-predicted-shrink-lending-rules-bed-demand-borrowers-remains-strong.html" data-desc="Mortgages will get harder to come by as lending rules take hold, warns Bank of England">Credit data has confirmed lenders expect the rate of household loan approvals to fall significantly in the coming months as tougher lending rules bed in.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664462/Ofgem-set-launch-investigation-energy-companies.html" data-desc="Ofgem set to launch full investigation into energy companies that could lead to break-up of the Big Six">The energy regulator is set to ask the Competition Market Authority to begin the investigation into whether the big energy suppliers are ripping off customers.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2669492/Private-rental-sector-not-fit-purpose-Labour-says.html" data-desc="'Make three-year tenancies the norm': Labour calls for greater stability in rental market as it warns sector is 'not fit for purpose'">Emma Reynolds, the shadow housing minister, said Britain had 'one of the most short-term, insecure and unstable' private rented sectors in Europe.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2664513/Business-rate-increases-killing-Britains-high-streets-shoppers-say.html" data-desc="Business rate increases are killing Britain's high streets, shoppers say">Shoppers would support action to cut business rates, retail campaigners say, after a survey found local taxes were seen as the biggest problem for town centres.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2665848/Super-Isa-washout-Majority-public-not-aware-new-tax-free-savings-limit.html" data-desc="Super Isa washout? Majority of public are unaware of new tax-free savings limit while just a third of those who do will add to their nest egg">From 1 July, savers can top up their tax-free Isas to &#194;&#163;15,000 and the full allowance can be held in a cash Isa, a significant lift from the current &#194;&#163;5,940 limit.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2665283/FCA-boss-Martin-Wheatley-Bankers-enforce-lending-rules-unfairly.html" data-desc="Fears of stringent cap on mortgage lending as financial watchdog says no need for banks to keep borrowers on higher-rate deals">FCA boss Martin Wheatley said he was disappointed, adding: &#226;&#8364;&#732;It shows some lenders are not approaching the rules in the spirit that they were intended. &#226;&#8364;&#732;They have to decide what level of risk they are prepared to take. That&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s reasonable. &#226;&#8364;&#732;But every firm also has a responsibility to treat their customers fairly...&#226;&#8364;&#8482;</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/bills/article-2664447/Dont-caught-big-holiday-phone-bill-Using-mobile-abroad-cost-thousands-follow-roaming-guide.html" data-desc="Don't get caught with a big holiday phone bill: Using your mobile abroad could cost thousands - so follow our roaming guide">The cost of using a mobile phone to dial home or browse the internet while you are abroad remains stubbornly high. Bills can top hundreds or even thousands of pounds if you use your mobile or tablet to listen to music, watch films or just to get directions. We look at ways families can cap charges while on holiday.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2665276/Britains-economy-growing-fastest-rate-2007.html" data-desc="Britain's first quarter growth could reach 0.9% with data expected to show economy growing at fastest rate since 2007">The Office for National Statistics will release a first-quarter growth revision, with research firm IHS Global Insight.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2664456/Start-saving-youll-need-bigger-deposit-buy-house.html" data-desc="It's still possible for average earners to buy a home but start saving now - you'll need a bigger deposit">Big could soon be beautiful again when it comes to saving a deposit for a first home. Earlier this month Bank of England boss Mark Carney and Chancellor George Osborne hinted that new borrowers will have to put a lot more money down to secure a loan. They also suggested that strict new lending limits could be imposed and that rate rises could come far sooner than expected.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2663510/Virgin-Money-boosts-rates-fixed-rate-cash-Isas-accepts-transfers.html" data-desc="Boost for savers as Virgin Money unveils best-buy cash Isa options that will allow transfers in">Virgin Money has today increased rates on a number of fixed-rate cash Isas with less than two weeks to go until the tax-free Isa limit increases to &#194;&#163;15,000.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2664487/You-guide-modern-ISA-Your-New-Individual-Savings-Account-nicer-sure-pick-best.html" data-desc="Your guide to the modern ISA: Your New Individual Savings Account will be nicer, but be sure to pick the best">The Isa revolution is almost here. From the start of next month you can open a tax-friendly New Individual Savings Account with up to &#194;&#163;15,000, put the whole amount in cash if you want and switch your old equity Isas into cash for the first time. Follow our guide to the modern Isa.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/experts/article-2664453/TONY-HETHERINGTON-Son-cancelled-dads-health-cover-operation.html" data-desc="'I've been left with hospital bills of £3k because health cover was cancelled days before operation': TONY HETHERINGTON investigates">I have been left with hospital bills of more than &#194;&#163;3,000 because PruHealth refused to pay the hospital and my consultant, despite authorising my treatment in writing. I also telephoned 24 hours before undergoing the procedure and the hospital checked on the day of the treatment. I am receiving pension credits, live in a housing association scheme for the over-60s and I am receiving demands from debt collectors.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2663547/Landlords-returns-hit-four-year-high-amid-rising-house-prices-renting-gets-cheaper.html" data-desc="Landlord returns hit four-year high amid rising house prices but rents rise by less than inflation">The average landlord in England and Wales has seen a return of &#194;&#163;20,133 in real terms in the last twelve months, or 12.2%, up from 5.3% the previous year.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2662510/I-thought-Post-Office-safe-place-money-Fraudsters-ransack-40-000-pension-pot-phone.html" data-desc="'I thought the Post Office would be a safe place to keep our money': Fraudsters ransack £38,800 pension pot over the phone">Any instance of bank fraud is distressing, but when the cash taken is a significant chunk of your pension, and money you had planned on gifting to your child to help buy their first home, the impact is even more shocking. That fate befell one This is Money reader, who then faced an anxious wait to see if their bank would make good a loss of &#194;&#163;38,800 that had been stolen from their Post Office savings account.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/pensions/article-2666927/Savers-ignorant-basic-pension-rules-hope-year-sweeping-Budget-reforms-introduced.html" data-desc="Fears retirees are headed for mass confusion as savers are ignorant of basic pension rules ahead of sweeping reforms">With upcoming reforms offering a myriad of options for savers, a survey has found that some already struggle to understand even the most basic of existing pension rules.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/bills/article-2665715/Coffee-snacks-cost-workers-2-500-year-say-dont-factor-spending-daily-budgets.html" data-desc="Coffee and snacks cost workers more than £2,500 a year - but a third say they don't factor spending into their daily budgets">Commuters across the UK will typically spend &#194;&#163;3.69 on lunch, the survey of more than 2,100 found. Meanwhile hot drinks sets the average worker back &#194;&#163;2.09.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2667392/CITY-FOCUS-Five-greatest-threats-global-economy.html" data-desc="Flashpoints that could spell catastrophe: Five great threats to the global economy">When the International Monetary Fund produced its April 2014 forecast of 3.6 per cent global output for the current year it added an important caveat. It warned that geopolitical factors, at the time mainly thought to be the turmoil in the Ukraine, posed a potential threat to its projections. This summer there are five major geopolitical flashpoints, each of which, potentially, poses a threat to economic stability.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2668186/Your-old-cash-Isa-beats-new-Super-Isa-stakes.html" data-desc="Savers looking to squeeze as much tax-free interest as possible from new Super Isa could earn more by topping up old closed accounts than from new deals">A handful of older accounts shut to new savers, but still open to existing customers, pay better rates than those on offer today.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2667233/Troubled-Tesco-sees-director-head-doors.html" data-desc="Troubled supermarket giant Tesco sees another director head for the doors">It is understood that UK general merchandise director Neela Mukherjee has been forced out following a reshuffle of the management team earlier this month.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2664345/Six-golden-rules-taking-houseguests.html" data-desc="Friends saving money by staying in your spare room this summer? Six golden rules of taking houseguests">House guests are fine but how do you get rid of them, asks Max Davidson. Nobody can avoid putting up the occasional house guest, but the experience will be far less stressful if you obey the six Golden Rules:</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/experts/article-2663884/Should-I-convert-US-university-bursary-dollars-I-American-bank-account-in.html" data-desc="Should I convert my £2k bursary for year at US university into dollars now - and should I get an American bank account to put it in?">My year out, as part of my university course, is in America in September and I am in the process of arranging my finances for the US. With the pound being so strong at the moment should I exchange my bursary of &#194;&#163;2,000 into dollars now to save constant currency exchanges and possible fluctuations over the next year?</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/comment/article-2667039/How-I-make-sure-savings-dont-run-I-die.html" data-desc="GUEST COMMENT: Pension shake-up means careful saving is no longer enough - risk is necessary to give the retirement income we need">Annuities have become more expensive due to our ever increasing life expectancy, coupled with record low yields on the assets that underpin them.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-2442541/How-research-investment-fund.html" data-desc="What should you know before buying a fund? The DIY investors'guide">Investment companies have to produce a checklist of important details like charges and performance for each of their funds - but what do they leave out?</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/article-2666812/Heating-systems-transformed-Google-opens-Nest-smart-software-developers.html" data-desc="Will your heating soon be talking to your car and know when you've woken up? How smart software could soon transform your home">The move by Google means other companies will now be able to take advantage of the smart thermostat's software - which can be controlled remotely. It is already working with Mercedes-Benz, Whirlpool and Logitech to develop apps that will turn on the heating when you're driving home or the washing machine at the cheapest times of day.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/bills/article-2665978/RACHEL-RICKARD-STRAUS-Applying-new-boiler-funding-minefield.html" data-desc="RACHEL RICKARD STRAUS: Do you know your GDHIF from your ECO and RHI? No?! That is why our homes are not more energy efficient">There are billions of pounds available for households to improve the efficiency of their homes. But applying for it is so complicated it's no surprise uptake is so low. Energy companies and government are dying to give out free boilers and insulation - but you'll have to get your head around GDHIFs, ECOs, CSCOs etc first.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/investing/article-2663764/Five-investment-funds-weather-market-sell-off.html" data-desc="Five funds to weather a market sell-off: The flashpoints for another crisis and where to shelter your investments in stormy times">Markets are still riding high but financial experts are getting increasingly concerned that a correction or even a crash is looming. Jason Hollands, managing director at investment specialist Bestinvest, offers fund tips for people looking to shelter their money in case markets turn stormy again.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-1616086/Fund-trust-ideas-time-cautious-investors.html" data-desc="INVESTING TIPS: Fund and trust ideas for beginner and cautious investors">If you are new to investing then the huge number of funds and investment trusts on offer can be confusing. Fortunately, This is Money's experts have some ideas to get you started.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/comment/article-2664478/JEFF-PRESTRIDGE-Its-smart-nervous-UK-shares-boom.html" data-desc="JEFF PRESTRIDGE: It's smart to be nervous about UK shares boom as higher annual Isa allowance nears">While the last five years have proved lucrative for those who have invested in UK equities - the FTSE 100 index alone has generated a return after reinvestment of dividends of 91 per cent according to stockbroker Brown Shipley - it doesn't mean that the next five years are going to prove as rewarding. There are numerous investment experts who are now nervous about where markets are heading.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/pensions/article-2669080/Just-1-4-trust-not-profits-provide-pension-guidance.html" data-desc="Only a quarter of over-55s trust not-for-profit groups to provide pensions guidance promised to all retirees">A survey also found there is little appetite among savers for insurance firms to be involved in providing the 'impartial, face-to-face' retirement guidance.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/experts/article-2667901/ASK-TONY-Dodgy-British-Gas-meter-charged-students-2-000.html" data-desc="ASK TONY: Dodgy British Gas meter charged our student house £2,000 for a few months' electricity">We gave a reading and British Gas said the meter must be faulty. But it's not resolved and we'll soon go our separate ways, so need to get this sorted.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-2667294/How-easy-investments-cash-Nisa.html" data-desc="Isas are set to be supercharged -  but how easy will it be to move your tax-free investments and cash?">Savers and investors will have more money to put away and shield from the taxman, and the freedom to move as little or as much of their &#194;&#163;15,000 allowance.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2668857/Virgin-Money-raises-rate-1-3-new-savers.html" data-desc="Virgin Money raises rate to 1.3% for new savers on easy-access account with no withdrawal restrictions">Virgin Money will allow savers in older issues earning less interest to switch into the latest version and it can be opened over the internet, post or in branch.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2668875/Taxman-shuts-281-walk-help-centres.html" data-desc="Taxman shuts down last of 281 walk-in help centres and replaces offices with telephone service">For the hard of hearing unable to use the phone and those with complex problems, HMRC will arrange for advisers to visit your home.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2669167/CBI-Retail-sales-slowdown-May.html" data-desc="CBI: Retail sales slowdown in May as England's early exit dampens hopes for a sales boost">The latest CBI distributive trade survey found that retail sales fell to a seven month low in May, with just a positive 4 per cent balance of retailers saying sales volumes were up.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/news/article-2667840/SAM-DUNN-Dont-shy-pays-haggle-bargain.html" data-desc="SAM DUNN: 'Cheeky', 'impudent' and 'rude' are often used to describe it, but don't be shy - it pays to haggle">Many won&#226;&#8364;&#8482;t entertain the notion of haggling. They cite discomfort at what is, squaring up to the retailer to challenge them on what you think goods are worth.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2668885/HSBC-abandons-travellers-cheques.html" data-desc="HSBC customers urged to cash in travellers cheques as bank stops accepting them from Friday">Customers who miss the deadline will be forced to go elsewhere, such as their local post office, where they may not get as good a rate.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2666871/Mortgage-loan-approvals-fall-9-month-low-May-loan-amounts-stay-26-higher-year-Bank-plans-act.html" data-desc="Number of mortgages approved at nine-month low but loans are larger">Mortgage approvals were 3.5 per cent lower in the month compared with a year earlier as new affordability rules took hold, the British Banker&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s Association said.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2664928/MIDAS-SHARE-TIPS-Dividend-Surprises-slips-beats-FTSE-350.html" data-desc="MIDAS SHARE TIPS: Our 'Dividend Surprises' portfolio slips but still knocks the spots off the FTSE 350 index">Of the ten shares in the group, six have lost value since we last looked at them in February. Even so, the portfolio has continued to outperform the FTSE 350 index, against which it is measured. The strategy we are using also has a long-term track record of success, so investors should give it a chance. The column looks at the ten companies in the FTSE 350 whose latest dividend payments most exceeded brokers&#226;&#8364;&#8482; expectations.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669588/RBS-chairman-Sir-Philip-Hampton-refuses-sides-independence.html" data-desc="Royal Bank of Scotland chairman Sir Philip Hampton refuses to take sides on Scottish independence ahead of September's referendum">Hampton warned that a 'Yes' vote created a 'great deal of uncertainty' over areas such as 'our credit rating, tax and regulation'. But he emphasised: 'We are not taking one side or the other and we will continue to maintain that neutral position.'</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-2663622/Cool-passion-stocks-fashion.html" data-desc="Out of fashion: Should investors sidestep the trend for over-hyped online retailers in favour of out-of-vogue 'value' stocks?">Since the astonishing success of ASOS enthusiasm grew around online retailers but should investors follow the herd or avoid in-vogue stocks? Stockopedia's Croft believes that while gossip around the hottest trends moves prices in any given year, it is company valuations versus fundamentals that drive prices in the long run.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669587/US-economy-bouncing-strongly-big-fall-output.html" data-desc="US economy bouncing back despite biggest fall in output since recession">GDP shrank between January and March but separate figures showed that services firms grew at the fastest pace for at least four-and-a-half years in June.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669602/Extraordinary-Bank-England-board-no-women-members.html" data-desc="Incoming chairman of Bank of England 'board' says it is 'extraordinary' it has no women members">Anthony Habgood, who succeeds Sir David Lees as chairman of the central bank&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s Court of Directors, told MPs that the lack of female representation was a problem.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2667266/Lord-Harris-decides-stay-Carpetright-chairman-found.html" data-desc="Lord Harris decides to stay at Carpetright until chairman is found">He was due to retire on September 4, leaving his post as executive chairman to make way for new chief executive Wilf Walsh.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/saving/article-2667234/Customers-soon-able-compare-current-accounts.html" data-desc="Millions of customers will soon be able to compare current accounts to see if they are getting a good deal from their bank">The Government announced it has agreed how the service will work said it would be up and running by the end of the financial year next March.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2667242/Heat-coming-housing-market-fall-mortgage-lending.html" data-desc="Bankers warn 'heat appears to be coming out of housing market' following fall in mortgage lending">The British Bankers&#226;&#8364;&#8482; Association said mortgage lending &#226;&#8364;&#8220; a good indicator of future sales &#226;&#8364;&#8220; fell last month amid a clamp down on risky home loans.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/mortgageshome/article-2662421/The-homebuyers-guide-How-best-home-secure-mortgage-ahead.html" data-desc="The homebuyer's guide: How to find the best home, secure a mortgage and get ahead in the property game">Whether you are looking to buy your first home or moving up the property ladder, we reveal the essential things for making your move successfully from finding the best home and securing the right mortgage for you to moving in and setting yourself up in your new home.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2666780/Engineer-Kentz-share-soar-33-1-9bn-Canadian-takeover.html" data-desc="Engineer Kentz sees shares soar on £1.9bn Canadian takeover">Montreal-based SNC-Lavalin said the &#194;&#163;1.16billion acquisition of the FTSE 250 company would enable it to carry out larger and more complex oil and gas projects.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/investing/article-2663983/Super-Isa-just-days-launch.html" data-desc="INVESTMENT EXTRA: How to use the new super Isa allowance - and why you should stick to the golden rules of investing">The all-singing, all-dancing new super Isa is just days from launch. From July 1 investors can put up to &#194;&#163;15,000 a year in tax-free savings and investments. This is a considerable boost to the current &#194;&#163;11,880 limit and, critically, it is the first time investors can switch out of equity Isas into the cash equivalents.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669609/MARKET-REPORT-Allergy-test-deal-pushes-Akers-Biosciences.html" data-desc="MARKET REPORT: Allergy test deal pushes up shares in diagnostic tool manufacturer Akers Biosciences
            FTSE CLOSE: Footsie tumbles on US figures
           ">Top-rated fund manager Rob Giles alerted everyone to the attractions of Akers late last year when he personally bought a 6.5 per cent stake. He has a big following in the City and many of his fans would have followed him in. Now news of a major US distribution deal with Medline Industries to determine if patients will have a reaction to blood thinner heparin has revived buying interest. The shares were chased up to 315p before closing 27.5p higher at 297.5p.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669589/Virgin-Media-chief-Tom-Mockridge-takes-old-boss-broadband-battle.html" data-desc="Clash of the titans: Virgin Media chief Tom Mockridge takes on old boss in broadband battle">The News Corporation trouble-shooter took charge of Britain&#226;&#8364;&#8482;s cable champion last year and now finds himself in a head-to-head battle with Rupert Murdoch.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669607/Sir-Stelios-Haji-Ioannou-raises-lower-hoped-30m-EasyHotel.html" data-desc="Serial entrepreneur Sir Stelios Haji-Ioannou raises lower-than-hoped £30m for assault on Europe by his 'super budget' hotel group">EasyHotel placed new shares worth &#194;&#163;30m, having earlier set itself a target of up to &#194;&#163;60m, amid investor weariness in the face of a flood of stock market listings.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/markets/article-2669608/Takeover-target-Shire-shuns-AbbVie-bid-company.html" data-desc="Shire shrugs off attempts by predator AbbVie to accelerate pursuit of company and quickly clinch £27bn deal">London-listed Shire reiterated its view that the offer 'fundamentally undervalued the company and its prospects' and advised shareholders to take no action.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/investing/article-2668925/Blackrock-Emerging-Europe-The-fund-investors-strong-stomach.html" data-desc="Blackrock Emerging Europe: The trust for investors with a strong stomach that invests in periphery countries">The trust invests in what is called emerging Europe - predominantly Russia, Poland, Hungary, Turkey and Ukraine - and seeks to make money from its hoped for growth. Investors&#226;&#8364;&#8482; interest in these regions is low and confidence in the markets is poor. That might sound off-putting, but it means shares are cheap and, should they recover, there are potentially big profits to be made.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/investing/article-2665943/SMALL-CAP-SHARES-TIPS-Obtala-Resources-sees-African-agriculture-ripe-development.html" data-desc="SMALL CAP SHARES TIPS: Obtala Resources sees African agriculture as ripe for development">Over the last year, the share price has more than doubled as milestones have been passed, growth opportunities seized and new goals targeted. The recent focus has been the group's two food processing businesses: one in Tanzania, East Africa, the other, a cannery in Lesotho.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-1718291/Pick-best-cheapest-investment-Isa-platform.html" data-desc="How to choose the best (and cheapest) DIY investing Isa - and our pick of the platforms">Choosing the right DIY platform is crucial but a wealth of choice and changes to charges have left many investors scratching their heads. We pick some of the best. We also highlight why investing in an Isa makes sense, as it should protect your hopefully growing investments from tax forever.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-1616089/ISA-INVESTING-TIPS-Fund-trust-ideas-income-investors.html" data-desc="INVESTING TIPS: Top fund and trust ideas for income investors">Income investing is not just for those who wish to draw on their portfolio, reinvested dividends are also a great way to build solid growth over time. Our experts give their fund and investment trust recommendations.</a><a href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/diyinvesting/article-1708425/ISA-INVESTING-TIPS-Emerging-market-funds-investment-trusts.html" data-desc="INVESTING TIPS: Top fund and trust ideas for emerging markets">If you're looking to add some flair to your investing Isa with emerging markets, This is Money's experts have some ideas to get you started</a></div></div>